udmserve.com 2013-05-02

# :: Welcome to Underdog Media Performance Unleashed ::

## We Take Your Privacy Seriously

**This privacy policy covers the site http://www.underdogmedia.com (marketing web site), http://udmserve.com (administration site), and http://udmserve.net (ad request site). Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy, we disclose the following information.**

1\. What personally identifiable information Underdog Media collects.  
---  
2\. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.  
3\. What organization collects the information.  
4\. How Underdog Media uses the information.  
5\. With whom Underdog Media may share user information.  
6\. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.  
7\. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Underdog Media control.  
8\. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.  
  
### Information Collection and Use

Underdog Media is the sole owner of the infomation collected on our web site. Underdog Media collects information at several different points on our Web site. 

Information is collected for the purpose of delivering advertisements. A user must provide the clickstream information (internet protocol address, internet service provider, platform type, date/time stamp, operating system), http protocol information (last uri requested and browser type), interaction information (browser interaction such as when the mouse moves over an image), interactive data (account activity and searches performed) and unique identifiers (login id or other id). The reason we use this information is to archive information for future reference, complete the current transaction, enhance our site and product offerings, maintain and secure our site and understand (in aggregate) interests of website visitors. We retain this information as stated by our business practices.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. You can set your browser to notify you to either accept or deny the cookies. Our client website uses cookies to enhance our site.

### Profiles

Underdog Media does not create a user profile.

### Opt-Out Informations

Underdog Media provides an "opt-out cookie" that allows users to opt-out of all our advertising cookies. Please be advised that you will continue to receive advertising. We will, however, no longer track what advertisements you have seen. Note that if you delete your opt-out cookie, you must opt-out again. To opt-out of all Underdog Media tracking cookies [click here.](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)

### Communications from the Site

Underdog Media does not use contact information to contact users in any manner.

### Sharing Information

Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

Personally Identifiable Information  
Personally identifiable information is not shared with any third parties.

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)  
Aggregate information is not shared with any third parties.

### Data Security

Underdog Media has physical security in our facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information. Our company uses secure encryption technology (secure socket connection) for all sensitive financial or health data transmitted on our site.

### Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes such as zip code, phone, email or postal address they can change all information. If a user wishes to correct/update information or no longer desires our service, they can notify us of what they desire by contacting us using any of the information in the Contact section of this policy.

### Links and Advertisements

Our website contains links to other sites. We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. We, Underdog Media, are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### Changes to the Privacy Statement

The information you submit to us is controlled by the privacy policy in effect at the time you submit it. If we significantly change our policy, we will reserve the right to apply this change to any and all data previously collected before the change was made.

### Data Retention Statement

Stated Business Practices Data retention - We keep information about you and your purchases for as long as you remain our customer. If you do not place an order from us for one year we will remove your information from our databases. Legal Requirement Data retention - We keep information about you for 4 years after you terminate employment in accordance with the employment practices established by CA EDD. Stated Purpose Data retention - We keep information about you until you have confirmed receipt of our product shipment plus the warranty period of 90 days. 

### Contact Information

Underdog Media, LLC  
10 E Yanonali St. Suite 2C  
Santa Barbara, CA 93101  
Email: admin@underdogmedia.com  
Phone: 805.880.6910  
Fax: 805.880.6917
